<item>
  <title>Captain's Log, Stardate 4784.6</title>
  <link>https://theta-ix.github.io/Enterprise-Archives-/feed/captain/the-heart-of-her-4784-6.html</link>
  <guid>https://theta-ix.github.io/Enterprise-Archives-/feed/captain/the-heart-of-her-4784-6.html</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[
Captain’s Log, Stardate 4784.6.

The Enterprise is en route to Starbase 12 for scheduled systems recalibration following sustained warp stress during recent survey operations along the Neutral Zone. Mister Scott assures me the strain is within acceptable tolerances. He does not sound pleased about it.

Minor fluctuations in the primary sensor array were detected approximately six hours ago. The readings were momentary — subtle enough to escape automatic diagnostics — but persistent enough to trouble Mister Spock. The anomaly does not correspond to any known stellar interference pattern.

What concerns me is not the fluctuation itself.

It is the pattern.

The signal appears intermittently. It does not repeat on a predictable cycle. Yet it is structured — almost as if responding to internal activity rather than external stimulus.

Engineering reports no malfunction. Computer analysis reveals no corruption in core memory. Structural integrity remains stable.

And yet.

There is a sensation aboard this ship — difficult to quantify — that something is attempting to assert itself. Not through force. Not through intrusion.

Through presence.

I have ordered a Level Three diagnostic of all major systems and restricted access to the primary computer core until we determine the source of the disturbance. In the meantime, the crew remains at standard readiness.

The Enterprise has encountered entities of vast power before — energy beings, incorporeal intelligences, civilizations hidden within stars.

If this is another such encounter, it is unlike any we have faced.

This one is not reaching in.

It feels as though it has always been here.

End log.
  ]]></description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2268 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
